question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The name of the main character of the video game &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, is Zelda.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Luigi is taller than Mario?",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The game &quot;Battlefield 1&quot; takes place during World War I.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;Half-Life 2&quot; runs on the Source Engine.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2005 video game &quot;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One&quot; is not available on PC.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Ana was added as a new hero for the game Overwatch on July 19th, 2016.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Bulbasaur is the only starter pokemon that is a Grass\/Poison type.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     }
]
